Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiocassettes, 1980 -- 1999; 1993 -- 1998; MS074.003; 2.2 Linear Feet; 17 Audiovisual Object(s)
  - Hughes mid-Am / Boyden, Mid-Am, 1996-06-08; MS074.003.071.00030 (Box 71)
    Originally located subject files series, in "Jorgensen, Leslie" file.
  - Ralph Reed, National Press Club, 1994-10-12; MS074.003.071.00031 (Box 71)
    Relocated from subject files series (Christian Colation "people - Reed, Ralph" file).
  - Meet at city hall PSA's / Support local church PSA's, MS074.003.071.00032 (Box 71)
    Relocated from subject files series ("Meet at city hall" file).
  - Terminal vision (global education), Eric Buehrer, MS074.003.071.00033 (Box 71)
    From NACE/CEE. Relocated from subject files series ("NACE/CEE - CEE suit" file).
  - Terminal vision (global education), Eric Buehrer, MS074.003.071.00034 (Box 71)
  - How to organize a CEE committee in your district, MS074.003.071.00035 (Box 71)
    From National Association of Christian Educators (NACE). Relocated from subject files series ("NACE/CEE - CEE suit" file).
  - CFV - the CFV approach, MS074.003.071.00036 (Box 71)
    Relocated from subject files series, "Colorado for Family Values" box.
  - CFV - Family research institute and closing, MS074.003.071.00037 (Box 71)
    Relocated from subject files series (Colorado for Family Values box).
  - Media - CFV, MS074.003.071.00038 (Box 71)
  - Opposition research - CFV, MS074.003.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - CFV - Special message, MS074.003.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - Putting it together, part I, 1993; MS074.003.073.00001 (Box 73)
    From Colorado for Family Values (CFV) National Seminar, 5/1/93. Relocated from subject files series ("Colorado for Family Values" box).
  - Putting it together part 2, MS074.003.073.00002 (Box 73)
    Relocated from subject files series ("Colorado for Family Values" box).
  - CFV - What we taught at the grassroots, MS074.003.074.00001 (Box 74)
- Videocassettes, 1984 -- 1998; 1987 -- 1998; MS074.004; 412 Audiovisual Object(s)
  Videotapes collected by the Institute for First Amendment Studies. Most were produced between 1987 and 1998. These tapes are part of IFAS' collection of information on the activities of conservative Christian groups, and involve figures and subjects associated with the Religious Right and IFAS founder Skipp Porteous. Most of the tapes were assigned index numbers by IFAS, and for this portion of the series the original, numerical order was preserved. This series includes tapes of the 700 Club's broadcasts, primarily between June, 1989 and January, 1991, with some tapes from 1995-1998. In addition, the collection includes videotapes from the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory meetings in 1991, 1993, 1994, 1995 and 1998.
  This series is arranged primarily numerically according to index provided by IFAS. Most of this series has been item-level cataloged, with the exception of tapes of broadcasts of "The 700 Club" television show, which have been boxed together and are not item-level cataloged. Unnumbered tapes were grouped at the end of the series. Tapes from the Christian Coalition's Road to Victory conferences are grouped together and alphabetized by speaker when not already numbered by IFAS; tapes from other sources are alphabetized by title. Also included are materials originally found in the subject files which were relocated to the videotape series. These last three groups are item-level cataloged.
  - The Big Lie, MS074.004.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Holland, 1984; MS074.004.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Beginning Again, MS074.004.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Adirondack Coalition For Choice, Skipp Porteous, 1993; MS074.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Religious Apartheid Featuring John Whitehead Of The Rutherford Institute, MS074.004.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Who Controls Our Children?, MS074.004.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Kingdom Of An Alien God, 1988-05; MS074.004.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - D. James Kennedy, 1989-06-04 -- 1989-07-09; MS074.004.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - D. James Kennedy, 1989-07-16 -- 1989-08-20; MS074.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Congress Exposed, MS074.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Pat Robertson At New Orleans Republican Convention, 1988-08-16; MS074.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - The Honorable Dan Quayle, 1991; MS074.004.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Christian Coalition Meeting, San Jose California, Bethol Church, 1992-02-29; MS074.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Christian Coalition, America At The Crossroads, MS074.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Pat Robertson, How To Turn America Back To God, MS074.004.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Paul Weyrich, Future Of The Pro-Family Movement, 1992; MS074.004.016.00001 (Box 16)
  - The Worst Of Pat R. For Skipp Porteous And Barbara Simon, The Freedom Writer, MS074.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - RTV1, Robertson Speech (2nd On Tape), RTV2 Robertson Speech (1st On Tape), MS074.004.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Panel Discussion, New York City School Board Races, 1993; MS074.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Pat Buchanan, Conservatives And Middle America, 1993; MS074.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Panel Discussion, The Real Anita Hill, 1993; MS074.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Mike Huckabee, Luncheon Address, 1993; MS074.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Jack Kemp, Strong Families And A Growing Economy, 1993; MS074.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Senator Don Nickels, Pat Rooney, Health Care Reform and The Family, 1993; MS074.004.024.00001 (Box data_value_missing_1b102f7ea03b1195c318081cfe9d1962)
  - Rep. Newt Gingrich, Renewing American Civilization, 1993; MS074.004.025.00001 (Box data_value_missing_1b102f7ea03b1195c318081cfe9d1962)
  - Pat Robertson, The Turning Tide: Decline Of Liberalism And Rise Of Common Sense, 1993; MS074.004.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Larry Burkett, Clintonomics and the Coming Economic Earthquake, 1993; MS074.004.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Oliver North, God and Country Banquet, 1993; MS074.004.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Dr. William Bennett, Turning The Tide Of America's Cultural Decline Gala Banquet, 1993; MS074.004.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - America at the Crossroads, How To Start A C.C. Chapter, The Gay Agenda, MS074.004.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Tim Phillips: Voter Targeting And Issues Management, MS074.004.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - David Miner: Fundraising, MS074.004.032.00001 (Box data_value_missing_2c2c061147982e446517bd59b53217f6)
  - Fundraising With Dick Weinhold For Christian Coalition Leadership School, Video Training Series, MS074.004.033.00001 (Box data_value_missing_12d86d392e785b9dddf15f7aaf48ed11)
  - David Miner: Fundraising, MS074.004.034.00001 (Box data_value_missing_2c2c061147982e446517bd59b53217f6)
  - Fundraising With Dick Weinhold For Christian Coalition Leadership School, Video Training Series, MS074.004.035.00001 (Box data_value_missing_12d86d392e785b9dddf15f7aaf48ed11)
  - Terry Cooper: Opposition Research, MS074.004.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Mike Murphy: Paid Media, MS074.004.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Verne Kennedy: Polling And Strategies., MS074.004.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Media And Spokesmanship With Rebecca Hagelin For Christian Coalition Leadership School, Video Training Series, MS074.004.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Rights And Wrongs Of The Religious Right With Paul Weyrich For Christian Coalition Leadership School Video Training Series, MS074.004.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Penny Pullen And Kevin Burnette: Framing The Pro-Life Issue, MS074.004.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Positive Confrontation: Learning To Win With Senator H.L. Richardson For Christian Coalition Leadership School Video Training Series, MS074.004.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Pat Robertson, Gala Banquet, MS074.004.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Marianne Dunn: Developing The Campaign Plan, MS074.004.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - America At A Crossroads, Christian Coalition 1990, & Firing Line Special On Religious Right (Sept. 1993), 1990 -- 1993; MS074.004.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - Roger Byrd: Effective Governing, MS074.004.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - 10th Anniversary Celebration, 6 Hour Version, 1989; MS074.004.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - 10th Anniversary Celebration, 6 Hour Version, 1989; MS074.004.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - 10th Anniversary Celebration, 6 Hour Version, 1989; MS074.004.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - The Decision: Anti-Semitism And The Church, MS074.004.050.00001 (Box 50)
  - Dobson/Porn, Abortion, The Temple, Armageddon, Rock Music, 1989; MS074.004.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - Hal Lindsey, Jerry Falwell, MS074.004.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Clinton's Circle Of Power, 1994; MS074.004.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Rev. Jerry Falwell Offering Clinton Expose Tapes - Knocking President, 1994; MS074.004.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - Family Congress, 1992-03-20; MS074.004.055.00001 (Box 55)
  - Creflo Dollar, 1994; MS074.004.056.00001 (Box 56)
  - Government Waste: Can America Survive It?, 1984; MS074.004.057.00001 (Box 57)
  - A Profile Of Faith, 1985; MS074.004.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - CAN Presentation @ Home Church In Campbell, CA, Speakers Are Bill Dannemeyer, Jay Grimstead, And David Barton, 1992-04-02; MS074.004.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - Randall Terry Out Takes, Satellite Uplink, 1993-07; MS074.004.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - PAFE - Meeting, 1994-03-30; MS074.004.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Jody Ripper, MS074.004.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Austin's EEQC Letter, Read By Ron Haus, Let's Get America Back To God, MS074.004.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Damned In The USA, MS074.004.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Oral Roberts, 1987; MS074.004.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - Swaggart Attacks Dominion Theory, Manif. Sons, And Sheparding (W.D. Hunt), 1986; MS074.004.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - The Bible Speaks - Roger Mudd, Swaggart, 1986-11-23; MS074.004.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Swaggart 7/12, 19, 28, 8/2, Roberts 7/12 & 19, 1987; MS074.004.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Falwell 9/6, 700 Club 9/2, Falwell 8/23, Roberts 8/23, Robert Tilton 9/1, Falwell 9/13, Robertson...9/13, 1987; MS074.004.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - Bruce Baden: Founding Fathers And Religious Freedom, MS074.004.070.00001 (Box 70)
  - America's Godly Heritage, David Barton, 1990; MS074.004.071.00001 (Box 71)
  - Russian, World War III...And Armageddon, 1989; MS074.004.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - Outcome-Based Education, 1993; MS074.004.073.00001 (Box 73)
  - Mebbe So Huh! With Willy Whitefeather, MS074.004.074.00001 (Box 74)
  - Voter Registration With Senator H.L. Richardson And Barbara Alby, Featuring Reverend Ty Beeson, MS074.004.075.00001 (Box 75)
  - The Other Israel, With Ted Pike, National Prayer Network, MS074.004.076.00001 (Box 76)
  - ACTV How To Win An Election, MS074.004.077.00001 (Box 77)
  - Life And Liberty For All Those Who Believe, MS074.004.078.00001 (Box 78)
  - People For The American Way, 5 Video Spots, MS074.004.079.00001 (Box 79)
  - One Nation Under God, MS074.004.080.00001 (Box 80)
  - Linda Thompson's Waco, The Big Lie As Presented By The Traditional Values Coalition, MS074.004.081.00001 (Box 81)
  - Waco, Texas By Linda Thompson, MS074.004.082.00001 (Box 82)
  - Cults: Saying No Under Pressure, MS074.004.083.00001 (Box 83)
  - Adult Video Association PSA, MS074.004.084.00001 (Box 84)
  - Voices From The Front, By Testing The Limits, 1992; MS074.004.085.00001 (Box 85)
  - Gay Youth: An Educational Video For The Nineties, MS074.004.086.00001 (Box 86)
  - Gay Agenda/Gay Rights - Special Rights, Gay Conspiracy - Voices From The Front, Gay Youth, MS074.004.087.00001 (Box 87)
  - Stonewall, 25 Years Of Deception, MS074.004.088.00001 (Box 88)
  - The Gay Agenda In Public Education, MS074.004.089.00001 (Box 89)
  - The Gay Agenda, The March On Washington, 1993; MS074.004.090.00001 (Box 90)
  - Gay Rights/Special Rights, 1993; MS074.004.091.00001 (Box 91)
  - The Gay Conspiracy, MS074.004.092.00001 (Box 92)
  - Freedom Is Your Business, MS074.004.093.00001 (Box 93)
  - The First Amendment In Crisis, A Look At The Rise Of Censorship And Intolerance In America, MS074.004.094.00001 (Box 94)
  - Experience The Freedom Of The Naturist Lifestyle, 1992; MS074.004.095.00001 (Box 95)
  - Baring The Threat: A Look At Religious Extremism, 1993; MS074.004.096.00001 (Box 96)
  - Baring The Threat, Revision #2, Dub From Sub-Master, 1993; MS074.004.097.00001 (Box 97)
  - Skipp Porteous Talk, Planned Parenthood, MS074.004.098.00001 (Box 98)
  - Skipp Porteous, Iowa Inquiry, Richard Eychaner, 1992; MS074.004.099.00001 (Box 99)
  - Russ Bellant, Iowa Inquiry, Rich Eychaner, 1992; MS074.004.100.00001 (Box 100)
  - Skipp Porteous Debating Jerry Falwell, 1988; MS074.004.101.00001 (Box 101)
  - Morton Downey Jr. Show, Falwell Vs. Skipp Porteous, 1988-04-12; MS074.004.102.00001 (Box 102)
  - Skipp Porteous, 1993-03-27; MS074.004.103.00001 (Box 103)
  - Skipp Porteous On CNN, With The Non-Burning Flag, 1989-06-29; MS074.004.104.00001 (Box 104)
  - Skipp On WOR TV, 1986; MS074.004.105.00001 (Box 105)
  - The Michigan Intellectual Freedom Coalition, MS074.004.106.00001 (Box 106)
  - Eye To Eye With Connie Chung (Master), 1993; MS074.004.107.00001 (Box 107)
  - Pozner & Donahue, 1992-02-23; MS074.004.108.00001 (Box 108)
  - People Are Talking, WBZ-TV, Ch. 4 Boston, Bebate With Jerry Falwell, 1984-12-17; MS074.004.109.00001 (Box 109)
  - People Are Talking WBZ, Boston, Debate With Jerry Falwell (Master, Edited), 1984-12-17; MS074.004.110.00001 (Box 110)
  - Exit Counselor Ric Ross On Geraldo 9/7/88, Dershowitz/Robertson, Skipp On Downey 9/20/88 Strodes, 1988-09; MS074.004.111.00001 (Box 111)
  - People Are Talking WWOR TV, Skipp Porteous, Pledge Of Allegiance, Richard Bey, Host, 1988-10-05; MS074.004.112.00001 (Box 112)
  - Full Gospel Business Men's Fellowship International World Convention International Breakfast, 1994; MS074.004.113.00001 (Box 113)
  - International Pastors And Ministers Conference, N.J. July - Rev. Dollar - God Ordains Interracial Marriage - Sound Bites Re: Whites, 1994; MS074.004.114.00001 (Box 114)
  - Militia Of Michigan, MS074.004.115.00001 (Box 115)
  - Militia Of Montana, MS074.004.116.00001 (Box 116)
  - America In Peril By Mark Koernke, America In Peril 1, MS074.004.117.00001 (Box 117)
  - A Cosmic Christmas Celebration, Global Peace Foundation, MS074.004.118.00001 (Box 118)
  - CTSB Announcements, Candidates Forum, Great Barrington, 1994-05; MS074.004.119.00001 (Box 119)
  - Pozner & Donahue, Skipp Porteous, Jay Grimstead, John Guest & Vladmir Pozner & Phil Donahue, 1992-02-23; MS074.004.120.00001 (Box 120)
  - Jay Sekulow, Defending Religious Liberty, 1994; MS074.004.121.00001 (Box 121)
  - Senator Phil Gramm (R-TX), Family-Friendly Health Care Reform, 1994; MS074.004.122.00001 (Box 122)
  - Christian Coalition Live, 1995-02-21; MS074.004.123.00001 (Box 123)
  - Christian Coalition Live, With Dr. Ralph Reed, Jr., 1995; MS074.004.124.00001 (Box 124)
  - David Barton, America's Godly Heritage, 1994; MS074.004.125.00001 (Box 125)
  - Dr. Pat Robertson, 5th Anniversary Banquet, 1994; MS074.004.126.00001 (Box 126)
  - Bishop Knox, Principal, Protestant Layman Of The Year, 1994; MS074.004.127.00001 (Box 127)
  - Hon. Dick Cheney, 5th Anniversary Banquet, 1994; MS074.004.128.00001 (Box 128)
  - Michael Medved, Hollywood Vs. America, 1994; MS074.004.129.00001 (Box 129)
  - Dr. D. James Kennedy, True Christian Citizenship, 1994; MS074.004.130.00001 (Box 130)
  - Dr. Ralph Reed, Jr., Politically Incorrect...And Proud, 1994; MS074.004.131.00001 (Box 131)
  - Rabbi Daniel Lapin, Jews And Christians In Unity, 1994; MS074.004.132.00001 (Box 132)
  - With God On Our Side - The Rise Of The Religious Right In America 1960-1992, MS074.004.133.00001 (Box 133)
  - America's Constitutional Heritage, Religion And Our Public Schools, MS074.004.134.00001 (Box 134)
  - Elizabeth Dole, Personal Testimony, 1994; MS074.004.135.00001 (Box 135)
  - Former Vice President Dan Quayle, Standing Firm, 1994; MS074.004.136.00001 (Box 136)
  - Rev. Peter Marshall, The Faith Of Our Founders, 1994; MS074.004.137.00001 (Box 137)
  - Phil Driscoll, Entertainment, 1994; MS074.004.138.00001 (Box 138)
  - D.J. Gribbin/Roberta Combs, Organizing Your Neighborhood, 1994; MS074.004.139.00001 (Box 139)
  - Dr. William Bennett, The Politics Of Virtue, Part 1, 1994; MS074.004.140.00001 (Box 140)
  - Dr. William Bennett, The Politics Of Virtue, Part 2, 1994; MS074.004.141.00001 (Box 141)
  - Gov. Robert Casey (D-PA), Remaining Pro-Life In Politics, 1994; MS074.004.142.00001 (Box 142)
  - What Is Summit Ministries, 1994; MS074.004.143.00001 (Box 143)
  - Americans Abandoned, MS074.004.144.00001 (Box 144)
  - Christian Coalition - Live Satellite Broadcast, 1995-03-21; MS074.004.145.00001 (Box 145)
  - The Children Of Table 34, The True Story Behind Alfred Kinsey's Infamous Sex Research, 1994; MS074.004.146.00001 (Box 146)
  - Congressman Bob Dornan: In His Own Words, MS074.004.147.00001 (Box 147)
  - Understanding Homosexuality And The Reality Of Change, MS074.004.148.00001 (Box 148)
  - AT&T Customer Training Video, MS074.004.149.00001 (Box 149)
  - Vallejo City Council Meeting, Norman Reese - Picketer, MS074.004.150.00001 (Box 150)
  - Hollywood Vs. Religion, The Truth Behind Hollywood's Hostility Toward Religion, 1994; MS074.004.151.00001 (Box 151)
  - New World Order, MS074.004.152.00001 (Box 152)
  - Dr. Gregg Dixon & Bob Fletcher Story, MS074.004.153.00001 (Box 153)
  - Mark Koernke In Columbus Ohio, MS074.004.154.00001 (Box 154)
  - Mark Koernke At: Justice Pro-Se, 1994-10; MS074.004.155.00001 (Box 155)
  - Tactical Update, With Mark Roernke (From Michigan), MS074.004.156.00001 (Box 156)
  - Tactical Update II, MS074.004.157.00001 (Box 157)
  - Sexuality Education For The 21st Century, 1995; MS074.004.158.00001 (Box 158)
  - Merry X-Mas* Abortion Protests (Pkg), MS074.004.159.00001 (Box 159)
  - Unholy Alliance, 1995; MS074.004.160.00001 (Box 160)
  - Taking Of Liberties (Pete Peters), Dr. Kennedy Church Seizure, MS074.004.161.00001 (Box 161)
  - Christian Coalition Live, 1995-04-18; MS074.004.162.00001 (Box 162)
  - How To Start A Christian County Chapter With Guy Rodgers, MS074.004.163.00001 (Box 163)
  - New York State - Court Of Appeals, Oral Arguments, Grumet V. B.O.E. Kiryas Joel, 1993; MS074.004.164.00001 (Box 164)
  - Developing Your Campaign Plan And Message, Mark P. Campbell, MS074.004.165.00001 (Box 165)
  - Targeting Voters And Building Coalitions, Tim Phillips, MS074.004.166.00001 (Box 166)
  - Dealing With Teachers Unions, David Y. Denholm, MS074.004.167.00001 (Box 167)
  - Building An Effective Grassroots Organization, Mark P. Campbell, MS074.004.168.00001 (Box 168)
  - Developing And Implementing A Fundraising Plan, Tim Phillips, MS074.004.169.00001 (Box 169)
  - Winning As A Religious Conservative, Shelly A. Uscinski, MS074.004.170.00001 (Box 170)
  - Academic Standards And Outcome Based Education, Dr. Chester E. Finn, Jr., MS074.004.171.00001 (Box 171)
  - Education Reform And School Choice, David W. Kirkpatrick, MS074.004.172.00001 (Box 172)
  - Starting Your Local Chapter, With Ralph Reed, Jr., MS074.004.173.00001 (Box 173)
  - The Church Copyright License, MS074.004.174.00001 (Box 174)
  - Turning Point - The Order, MS074.004.175.00001 (Box 175)
  - Pat Robertson: In His Own Words, MS074.004.176.00001 (Box 176)
  - Road To Victory, Tape #1, Ralph Reed, Max Karren, 1995; MS074.004.177.00001 (Box 177)
  - AM At A Crossroads, 1990; MS074.004.178.00001 (Box 178)
  - Saturday Night: Gala Banquet, Oliver North, 1995; MS074.004.179.00001 (Box 179)
  - Saturday Night: Gala Banquet, Rev. E.V. Hill, 1995; MS074.004.180.00001 (Box 180)
  - Phil Driscoll, Music, 1995; MS074.004.181.00001 (Box 181)
  - Rep. Bob Dornan, America's Best Days Are Still Ahead, 1995; MS074.004.182.00001 (Box 182)
  - Rep. Dick Armey, A Dramatic Return To Limited Government, 1995; MS074.004.183.00001 (Box 183)
  - Rep. John Kasich, Why We Need A Family Friendly Budget, 1995; MS074.004.184.00001 (Box 184)
  - Dr. Bill Bennett, The Resurgence Of Virtue In America, 1995; MS074.004.185.00001 (Box 185)
  - Gov. Bob Casey, Raising The Pro-Life Standard In American Politics, 1995; MS074.004.186.00001 (Box 186)
  - Dr. Ralph Reed, The Role Of Religious Conservatives In The '96 Elections, 1995; MS074.004.187.00001 (Box 187)
  - Rep. Tom Delay, The Pro-Family Movement And The New Congress, 1995; MS074.004.188.00001 (Box 188)
  - Sen. Phil Gramm, How Washington Can Win America's Trust, 1995; MS074.004.189.00001 (Box 189)
  - Rep. Charles Stenholm, Democrats And The Pro-Family Movement, 1995; MS074.004.190.00001 (Box 190)
  - Gov. David Beasley, A Blueprint For Compassionate Welfare Reform, 1995; MS074.004.191.00001 (Box 191)
  - Kay James, How Limited Government Can Be A Friend Of The Family, 1995; MS074.004.192.00001 (Box 192)
  - Speaker Newt Gingrich, Renewing America, 1995; MS074.004.193.00001 (Box 193)
  - Star Parker, Escaping The Welfare Stranglehold, 1995; MS074.004.194.00001 (Box 194)
  - Sen. Bob Dole, Taking America Into The 21st Century, 1995; MS074.004.195.00001 (Box 195)
  - Rabbi Daniel Lapin, Jewish And Christian Unity, 1995; MS074.004.196.00001 (Box 196)
  - Saturday Night: Gala Banquet, Pat Buchanan (Invited), 1995; MS074.004.197.00001 (Box 197)
  - Saturday Night: Gala Banquet, Larnelle Harris, 1995; MS074.004.198.00001 (Box 198)
  - Sen. Richard Lugar, Optimism For The Future Of American Families, 1995; MS074.004.199.00001 (Box 199)
  - Chuck Colson, Christian's Vital Role In Government, 1995; MS074.004.200.00001 (Box 200)
  - Lamar Alexander, Walking A Steady Pace For America's Future, 1995; MS074.004.201.00001 (Box 201)
  - Judge Robert Bork, Examining Our Modern-Day Scales Of Justice, 1995; MS074.004.202.00001 (Box 202)
  - Dr. Alan Keyes, Returning To Moral Stability, 1995; MS074.004.203.00001 (Box 203)
  - Weyrich, Jackson, Williams, Talking Back To America, Mona Charen - Moderator, 1995; MS074.004.204.00001 (Box 204)
  - Phyllis Schlafly, Standing For Life, 1995; MS074.004.205.00001 (Box 205)
  - Jeane Kirkpatrick, America's Role As A World Leader, 1995; MS074.004.206.00001 (Box 206)
  - Jay Sekulow, Preserving Our Religious Liberties, 1995; MS074.004.207.00001 (Box 207)
  - Eckstein, Wittman, Uhlmann, Abrams, Our Judeo-Christian Heritage: A Partnership...Future, 1995; MS074.004.208.00001 (Box 208)
  - Dr. Gary Bauer, Challenges For The Pro-Family Movement In The 1990's, 1995; MS074.004.209.00001 (Box 209)
  - David Barton, Faith, Freedom And Heritage, 1995; MS074.004.210.00001 (Box 210)
  - Sen. Dan Coats, American Renewal, 1995; MS074.004.211.00001 (Box 211)
  - Lt. Gov. Mike Huckabee, A Grassroots Success Story, 1995; MS074.004.212.00001 (Box 212)
  - Peter Marshall, The Necessity Of Moral Leadership, 1995; MS074.004.213.00001 (Box 213)
  - The Ultimate Target Of The Gay Agenda, Same Sex Marriages, 1996; MS074.004.214.00001 (Box 214)
  - Road To Victory #2, Weyrich, 1995; MS074.004.215.00001 (Box 215)
  - Rep. Dick Armey, A Bold Plan To Strengthen Families By Reducing Government, 1996; MS074.004.216.00001 (Box 216)
  - David Barton, America's Godly Heritage, 1996; MS074.004.217.00001 (Box 217)
  - Pat Buchanan, America's Days Are Ahead, 1996; MS074.004.218.00001 (Box 218)
  - Sen. Dan Coats, How Faith And Compassion Can Make America Strong, 1996; MS074.004.219.00001 (Box 219)
  - Rep. Tom Delay, Charting A Course For A Pro-Family Congress, 1996; MS074.004.220.00001 (Box 220)
  - Deleon, Woodson, A Spiritual Rebirth Of Our Inner Cities, 1996; MS074.004.221.00001 (Box 221)
  - Bob Dole/Jack Kemp, America's Bright Prospects For The New Millennium, 1996; MS074.004.222.00001 (Box 222)
  - Rep. Bob Dornan, Faith, Freedom And Family, 1996; MS074.004.223.00001 (Box 223)
  - Rabbi Yechiel Eckstein, Strengthening Our Jewish And Christian Values, 1996; MS074.004.224.00001 (Box 224)
  - Speaker Newt Gingrich, Realizing The American Dream, 1996; MS074.004.225.00001 (Box 225)
  - Sen. Jesse Helms, Preserving Traditional Values, 1996; MS074.004.226.00001 (Box 226)
  - Gov. Mike Huckabee, 1996; MS074.004.227.00001 (Box 227)